Finding Aid for the W.W. Robinson papers, ca. 1843-1972
UCLA Library Special Collections
W.W. Robinson papers
ca. 1843-1972
2072
Robinson, W.W. (William Wilcox), 1891-
97 boxes (48.5 linear ft.) 7 oversize folders 13 oversize boxes
William Wilcox Robinson (1891-1972) wrote many pamphlets, articles, and books on Southern California history, including: Ranchos Become Cities (1939), Land in California (1948), Los Angeles, a Profile (1968), and Bombs and Bribery (1969). He also wrote poetry, fiction, children's books, and essays, and served on boards of numerous organizations. The collection contains manuscript and research materials, papers related to Robinson's civic, literary, and social activities. The collection also includes family and personal correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, and objects including awards, keepsakes, and decorations.
University of California, Los Angeles. Library Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF. Advance notice is required for access to the collection. Please contact UCLA Library Special Collections for paging information.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Estate of W.W. and Irene Robinson, 1972.
Biography/History
William Wilcox Robinson was born on May 1, 1891 in Trinidad, Colorado; moved to Riverside, California, in 1899; attended USC; AB, English, UC Berkeley, 1916; served in World War I; moved permanently to Los Angeles, California, in 1919; married Irene Bowen in 1923; while working as a professional property title researcher for the Title Guarantee (later named Insurance) and Trust Company in Los Angeles, and later as vice-president, he developed an extensive knowledge of local history and land development; wrote many pamphlets, articles, and books on Southern California history, including: Ranchos Become Cities (1939), Land in California (1948), Los Angeles, a Profile (1968), and Bombs and Bribery (1969); he also wrote poetry, fiction, children's books, and essays; founding president, the Friends of the UCLA Library; member, the Cultural Heritage Board of Los Angeles; he served on boards of numerous organizations, including the California Historical Society and the Southwest Museum; died September 1, 1972 in Beverly Hills, California.
Scope and Content
Collection contains manuscript and research materials such as clippings, transcripts of land commission proceedings, pamphlets, maps, Robinson's publications, copies of books, and newspaper and magazine articles. Includes papers related to Robinson's civic, literary, and social activities. Also includes family and personal correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, and objects including awards, keepsakes, and decorations.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Biographical
Family Correspondence
Social Correspondence
Business Correspondence
Biographical Summaries, etc.
Bibliography
Biographical Items
Articles
Family History
Civic, etc. Committees
Historical Societies - Advisory
Historical Associations
Libraries and Library Organizations
Political Organizations
Social Organizations
Writers' Organizations
Lectures
Diaries, Jottings, etc.
Travel Items, New York to Los Angeles
Consultant Activity
Memorabilia: Objects
Photographs
Photographs, publicity, business
Oversize material, includes all groups
Research material
Manuscript material - by other writers
Publication material - photographs
Miscellaneous
Collected by WWR
Collected by WWR, California
Collected by WWR, Chains of title
Collected by WWR, Land items
Abstracts of title - city, rancho properties
Land articles, rancho lists, etc
Robinson, Irene Bowen. Papers: personal and art related
Writings
Arranged according to the Hicks bibliography
Not in Hicks, but arranged according to Hicks bibliography
The Land and the People (history of T.I.T.)
Unpublished
Unpublished revisions
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
Robinson, W.W. (William Wilcox), 1891- --Archives.; Robinson, Irene B. (Irene Bowen), 1891.; Historians--California, Southern--Archival resources.; Authors, American--20th century--Archival resources.; Land titles--Research--California, Southern.
Related Material
From Land Titles to Book Titles [oral history transcript] / W.W. Robinson, interviewee. UCLA Oral History Department interview, 1982. Available at Library Special Collections, UCLA.
Container List
- Biographical - Family Correspondence.
  - World War I.
    - Letters to his Parents: Salutations: Dear folks or Dear parents.
      - 1918 February-March., 6 items, 19 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1918 April., 1 item, 1 piece. (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1918 May-July., 10 items, 43 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1918 August., 8 items, 17 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1918 September., 3 items, 10 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1918 October., 3 items, 9 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1918 November., 3 items, 14 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1918 December., 4 items, 20 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1919 January-April., 16 items, 53 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1919 May-June., 20 items, 67 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - To W.H. Robinson (his Father), 1918 August, October., 2 items, 3 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - To Mrs. F.E. Collier (his sister, Flora), 1918 February-October., 4 items, 14 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - To his Sister (Helen Robinson), 1918 August-1919 January., 2 items, 4 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - To Frank Forward, 1919 May., 6 items, 12 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 15)
      With this: letter from Carrol R. West, 1968 January.
  - Letters Received by WWR from his Family.
    - W.H. Robinson's Letters from a Trip to England, 1926 July-August., 6 items, 43 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Sent to WW and Irene Bowen Robinson. With these: Cunard Daily Bulletin, 1928 July 27.
    - From Henry R. Adams (his Nephew).
      - 1942-1943., 16 items, 33 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - 1944., 9 items, 24 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - 1945., 22 items, 24 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 19)
        Includes 12 snapshots.
      - 1946., 5 items, 16 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - 1947., 18 items, 31 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 21)
        Includes 10 snapshots.
      - 1949, 1951-1955, 1959-1960., 19 items, 41 pieces. (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - 1969, 1971. (Box 1, Folder 23)
        1969 item is photocopy, not to WWR. Includes 3 snapshots.
    - From Archbold H. Robinson (his Brother), 1966 November. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - From Nieces and Nephews and Their Children, 1964 and 1969. (Box 1, Folder 25)
      From Bill (son of Archbold?); from Mary. Includes Ronnie's football team; illustrated and written by Billy Wayne. n.d.
- Biographical - Social Correspondence.
  - Hager, Anna Marie and Everett.. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Includes bibliographical information about WWR.
  - Malcolmson, Esther and David.
    - 1942-1943. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 1944. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1946, 1953. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Powell, Lawrence Clark.
    - 1950-1952. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 1954-1956. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 1960, 1965-1966, 1969-1971. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - n.d.. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - A - L, 1935-1971 (inclusive), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Includes letters from: Margot Archer, Homer H. Boelter, Blanche and Robert Campbell, Ed Carpenter, Jimmie Hicks, Frederick Webb Hodge, Idwal Jones.
  - M - Z, 1935-1971 (inclusive), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Includes letters from: Patrice Manahan, Doyce B. Nunis, Jr., Madeleine and Lee Shippey, Edward Weston.
  - Printed and Written Invitations. 1959, 1964, 1966-1967, 1969, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Maps to Houses.. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Birth and Death Announcements, 1962, 1964. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Cards.
    - Cards received, 1948-1950, 1952, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Includes cards from: Mary and Conrad Buff, and Francis and Marjory Farquhar.
    - Cards with text sent by IBR and WWR.. (Box 2, Folder 15)
      About statue of Father Serra in the Plaza (1959), with text about yucca stalks, toyon berries (n.d.). Drawn and colored by IBR.
    - Cards sent with no text other than greeting. By IBR.. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Cards sent, not by IBR. Carbon of letter from WWR (1960).. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Changes of Address (Personal and Business), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Riverside High School, 1907-1909, 1959 June-July, 1964. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Letters, class diaries, reunions, etc.
- Biographical - Business Correspondence.
  - Cards and Announcements, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Various, collected.
  - Real Estate, Credit Card, Church, etc. 1963-1969. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Addresses, Messages and Reminders, v.d. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    (Jottings)
  - Various, 1962, 1967, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Business correspondence with booksellers.
  - Not Related to Specifc WWR Works, 1961. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Business correspondence with publisher.
  - Requesting References, 1964, 1966, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    With carbons of replies.
  - Public Relations and Research Questions, 1949, 1952, 1955., Carbons. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    (Title Insurance and Trust)
    Letters from: Glenn S. Dumke and Howard H. Quint (concern Santa Anita and Rancho San Pasqual, Westlake Park).
  - Various, 1962, 1971. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - WWR Personally, 1947, 1955-1956. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Clippings about Romance of the ranchos and an orientation film.
  - Dedication of Norwalk Square.
    - 1953-1954. Traces chain of title for property.. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Publicity, 1954. Newspaper clipping. Chain of title reproduced and photograph of WWR in Pacific Mutual home office news.. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Retirement Affairs.
    - Financial matters, 1944-1945, 1956. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Brochures and clippings, 1938, 1952, 1956, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Statements, Dawson's Book Shop.. (Box 2, Folder 32)
      Evidently a fund created upon WWR's retirement.
    - Letters received upon retirement, 1956. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Article, 1956. In: The Newsletter of California Land Title Association, vol.4 no.5 (1956 April-May).., pp.5-6. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Christmas Cards. Los Angeles (1847 and 1857).. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Drawn / colored by IBR. Text by WWR. For T.I.T. officials. Views of: Mission San Gabriel, Monterey, Santa Barbara from anchorage, Rancho Santa Anita, etc.
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    With Edward Kemp and Dorothy Drake.
  - Los Angeles Art Institute. Letter, 1958 January. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Enclosure To above letter: Los Angeles County employee, 1958 January. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Antiquarian Booksellers.. ., Southern California Chapter.
    - Directories., Copies. (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Includes northern California chapter.
    - Catalog, 1950., Copy. (Box 4, Folder 4)
      One hundred years of California statehood: an exhibit of material showing possible fields of collecting prepared by ABAA, Southern California group.
    - Bulletin no.1, 1956 November., Copy. (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Contains article by Lawrence Clark Powell.
  - Book Club of California.
    - Correspondence, 1940 September, 1952 August, 1954 May, and 1962 February-March. (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Includes letters from: Oscar Lewis.
    - Enclosure, to above letter.., Printed (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - News Release, 1951 March. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Rounce Coffin Club.
    - Correspondence, 1947 April. (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Letter to WWR, about winners of Western Books Exhibit, 1947.
    - Enclosure, to above letter.., Printed (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Invitation to Meeting, 1950 October. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Roxburghe Club of San Francisco.
    - Correspondence and Mimeographed Mailings (Various), 1954, 1956, 1962-1963, and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Rosters (Various), 1962, 1965, 1967, 1970-1971. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Printed Forms, Typed Addresses, etc. (Various).. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Printing Ephemera, 1968 April 9. (Box 4, Folder 15)
      In memoriam... Martin Luther King.
  - Sacramento Book Collectors Club.
    - Letter, 1958 February. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Roster, 1962. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Zamorano Club.
    - Correspondence.
      - 1947, 1950-1955. (Box 4, Folder 18)
        Letters from: Charles K. Adams, Ramon F. Adams, Robert O. Schad, Frederick Webb Hodge, Ward Ritchie, Jean Hersholt, and Henry H. Clifford.
      - 1955, 1963-1964, 1966, 1971-1972.. (Box 4, Folder 19)
        Letters from: Lawrence Clark Powell, Glenn S. Dumke, Dwight L. Clark, Robert Vosper, Roby Wentz, Albert Shumate, William F. Kimes, and Arthur Hamlin.
      - n.d.. (Box 4, Folder 20)
        Letters from: Roby Wentz, Fridolf Johnson, and Albert Shumate.
    - WWR President[?], 1954 March 3, April 7, May 5, June 5, and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Introductions of speakers.
    - Notes by WWR, n.d., Holograph. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Clippings about Members, 1952, 1954, 1962, and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - [Annual report of secretary/treasurer]. 1951 February 7, 1952 February 6, and 1953 February 11., Carbon typescripts. (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Addressed: To Board of Governors and members of Zamorano Club, Los Angeles.
    - Minutes, 1950 October 4, 1951 June 6, 1953, June 13, and 19? November 6. (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Rosters, Dated February of the following years: 1962-1965, and 1971-1972. A correction sheet, 197?.. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Notes by WWR, 1953, 1972, and n.d., Holograph. (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Visit to UCLA, 1962., Printed item. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The __________ Book Club is born, 1952[?]. Los Angeles[?].. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Outlines of Plans, 1947 and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence about the Zamorano Club, 1955 and 1972. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Photos of the Adobe and Press, 1910 and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - WWR's Description of the Adobe, n.d., 1 leaf. Holograph. Half leaf. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Publications Committee.
      - Correspondence, 1954 July and October, and 1965 September-October. (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Adams, Charles K., 1928 January 25-1952 March., Various pagings, ca. 75 leaves. Typescript (photostat?). (Box 4, Folder 35)
        Summary of meetings, roster, list of publications of Zamorano Club.
      - Statement of publications policy, n.d. Evidently written by WWR.., 2 leaves. Carbon typescript. (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Harmsen, Tyrus G. Zamorano Club: an historical sketch, 1955 Fall. In: Quarterly News Letter, vol.20 no.4 [Book Club of California].. (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Letter concerning the history of the club, 1959. (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Mimeographed memos concerning project for history of the club, 1959 March and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Publications Committee - Wagner Bibliography.
      - Correspondence, 1964 July, October-November. (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Holograph notes by WWR, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Axe, Ruth Frey, 1964 July 20., 17 leaves. Typescript. (Box 4, Folder 42)
        With author's holograph corrections and some by WWR as editor.
      - The published writings of Henry R. Wagner... Los Angeles, 1955. (Box 4, Folder 43)
        This copy contains erased editorial additions by WWR on title page.
      - [Powell, Lawrence Clark]. Henry R. Wagner and his work, 1957 April 1., 6 leaves. Typescript (ditto). (Box 4, Folder 44)
        Eulogy given at the services held by the Zamorano Club, Forest Lawn.
    - Publications Committee - Bancroft Project.
      - Correspondence, 1965 and n.d. (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Rosters, minutes, etc., 1957, 1965. (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Notes by WWR, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Letter from the Hagers, 1962 January 20. With enclosures.. (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Program, Name Tag. 1949, 1954. (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Biographical - Civic, etc. Committees.
  - California Bicentennial Commission.
    - Assembly Concurrent Resolution, 1966. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1967 August-1971 April. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Includes letters from: Robert H. Finch, Governor Ronald Reagan, and Henry H. Clifford.
    - Planning Documents, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Organizational plan; and The task of county chairmen for the Bicentennail; and Bicentennial activities suggestions for schools.
    - Dates, Reading Lists, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      List of dates and description of events in California's 200 - year history. Books for California's 200th anniversary.
    - Items from Historical Societies.
      - Mailings, resolutions, 1967-1968. (Box 5, Folder 5)
        From: California Historical Society, Conference of California Historical Societies, Historical Society of Southern California, etc.
    - Reports Presented to the Commission, 1967-1968. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      From: Mrs. Robert E. Fowler, consultant to the Lieutenant Governor, and Daniel J. Edelman, public relations firm.
    - Clippings, 1967. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Speech and News Releases From Lieutenant Governor Finch, 1968-1969. (Box 5, Folder 8)
      With holograph notes by WWR.
    - Meeting Notices and Agendas, 1968-1969. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1968-1969. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Rosters, 1968 and n.d. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Staff Reports, 1968 April-June and June-July. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Status Report, 1968 June 17. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - California Bicentennial News [newsletter of the Commission] (1969 May- ). vol.1 no.3-6 and vol.2 no.4.. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - News Releases, 1969 May-September. (Box 5, Folder 15)
      From Wolcott, Carlson Company, Incorporated, public relations.
    - News Release, 1969 September-1970 April. (Box 5, Folder 16)
      From the Commission (contact: Stuart Wilson, etc.).
    - Bicentennial Commission Major Brochure - Final Copy, 1969 May., [50] leaves. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - California Bicentennial Information Kit, 1969[?].. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Brochures Printed by the Commission, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Memoranda, 1970 January-February and n.d. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Brochures not Printed by the Commission, 1969. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Los Angeles County Bicentennial Committee.
      - Memo about projects, 1970 April. (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Minutes, 1970 March 31. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - California Centennials Commission.
    - California Centennials, official news letter. California Centennials Commission. vol.2 no.6, 1949 December. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - California Commemorative Society.
    - Correspondence, 1969 July-September and 1970 January-March. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Robinson, W.W. Important events in California history suitable for medallions, [1969].., 4 leaves. Carbon typescript. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Enclosures to Correspondence, v.d. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Photograph, 1969 July. (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Lieutenant Governor Ed Reinecke and California Bicentennial Queen Cindy Paden Presenting Michael Tobey, outdoor advertising executive, with a California Bicentennial Medallion...
  - Committee on Historical Monuments for the Civic Center Mall.
    - Correspondence, 1958 February-April and 1962. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from: Gustave O. Arlt.
    - Holograph notes by WWR, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committee to Preserve the History of Los Angeles.
    - Correspondence, 1961 August-September, November and 1962 February-March, June, and 1963 March. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Primarily with Julian Nava.
    - Mailings, 1961-1963., Mimeographed. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Agendas, 1961-1962. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      With holograph notes by WWR; other sheets with WWR's notes. Also news release from the Office of the Mayor Sam Yorty with WWR's notes.
    - Minutes, 1961 December-1962 November. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Organizational Material and Enclosures, 1961-1963. (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Includes rosters, statements about the history of Los Angeles, proposals for collecting material, and a draft copy of the ordinance establishing CHB.
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1962 April and n.d. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Heritage Board.
    - WWR Personally, 1963-1965, 1968-1970., Mimeographed. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Announcements of WWR's appointment to the CHB. Also official letters of appointment.
    - Correspondence, 1963-1970 and n.d. (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Includes letter from Mayor Sam Yorty. Topics inclue invitations, memos, criticism of manuscript.
    - Letters received upon WWR's retirement from the CHB, 1971 July and September. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Invitations, 1963-1967 and n.d. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Political mailers, 1966. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - WWR's holograph notes, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - The CHB and Pat Adler, n.d., 1 leaf. Typescript (carbon). (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Evidently a citation prepared by WWR.
    - Sketch of WWR; and his business cards.. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Reports, Legislation, Plans.
      - Annual reports, 1963 and 1964/65. (Box 6, Folder 17)
        1963 is 1st.
      - Southern California AIA proposals for creation of CHB, 1962[?].. (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - City ordnance 121,971 and summaries of history of CHB, 1962-1971 (inclusive).. (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Documents about expansion of CHB powers, 1966-1968. (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - CHB policy guide, 1969., 2 copies. (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Letter from Regional Planning Commission to CHB, 1969., Copy. (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - WWR's statement of Prop.1, 1964., 1 leaf. Typescript (carbon). (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Proposition 1 and park mailers, 1963-1964. (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Master plan agenda for Cultural Heritage Board. City of Los Angeles, 1966. By WWR.., 2 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Other Cities' Counterparts.
      - WWR's holograph notes, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - National legislation, 1966., Copies. (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - William Woolett reports, 1968-1969. (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - National Trust mailing, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - National Trust statements, 1964-1970. (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Santa Barbara Trust for Historic Preservation mailing, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Brochures from Seattle, Savannah, and San Antonio.. (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Destination 90, policies for planning:.. ., 1968 January. (Box 6, Folder 33)
        A citizen's book of planning recommendations for the San Fernando Valley.
      - Cards and calendar with historical information.. (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Clippings, 1964 and 1967. (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Preservation workshops, 1965-1969 and n.d. (Box 6, Folder 36)
        Mailers, programs, etc.
    - Working Papers.
      - Rosters, 1964 and n.d. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - 1963. (Box 7, Folder 2)
        Usually with enclosures.
      - Memos from Ileana Welch.
        - 1964. (Box 7, Folder 3)
        - 1965. (Box 7, Folder 4)
        - 1966. (Box 7, Folder 5)
        - 1967. (Box 7, Folder 6)
        - 1968. (Box 7, Folder 7)
        - 1969. (Box 7, Folder 8)
        - 1970. (Box 7, Folder 9)
        - 1971. (Box 7, Folder 10)
        - 1964-1967, 1969-1972. (Box 7, Folder 11)
          Usually headed Notice or Announcement, and usually concerning meeting dates, statements of elected officers, etc.
        - 1964, 1966-1970 and n.d.. (Box 7, Folder 12)
          Usually headed Notice or Announcement, and usually concerning particulars for ceremonies of dedication of cultural heritage landmarks, exhibitions.
      - Documents from city planning departments, 1967 December and 1968 August, and, 1971. (Box 7, Folder 13)
        Cultural and historical monuments plan, and, Brief summary of. .. proposal for Pueblo de Los Angeles historical monument Placita Pedestrian Mall.
      - Memos from Clair Pirone and Ileana Welch, 1963 (IW), 1964 (CP), and 1965-1966 and 1969-1971 (IW). (Box 7, Folder 14)